simplysup.com 2013-11-01

# Trojan Remover - Privacy Policy

|  |    |   
---|---|---|---  
| 

|   |    
  
Here at Simply Super Software we are strongly committed to protecting your privacy.

When you visit the Simply Super Software website you are not required to disclose any personal information. We do collect anonymous statistics on visits to our website, including (but not necessarily limited to) referring domains, browsers used, platforms used, search phrases and search engines used. We do not track individual users' navigation details. No cookies are used for this purpose.

If you purchase a registration for Trojan Remover, the third-party registration company you use collects personal identification information which it passes to us. We require this information for our own records, and to be able to assist you in the future. The information which we are provided (and store securely) is your name, company name, email address, and postal address. We are also supplied with your telephone number (if you provide one) - however we do not retain the telephone number.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Third-party cookies may be installed on your system as part of this process, unless you opt-out. If you would like more information about this practice and would like to know your options in relation to not having this information used by these companies, please [ click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "Google Ads Privacy Policy").

Simply Super Software will not sell, rent or trade your personal information to any other party. Your personal information will not be disclosed to any third party unless we are required to do so by law.

**Cookies**  
Third parties may use cookies on this site, as part of our participation in Google Adsense. These cookies provide our advertising partners with information about your visit to this site so that they can offer targetted adverts. You can find out more about cookies, including how to disable them in your browser, at AboutCookies.org.

Information on how to contact Simply Super Software is on the  Contact Us page.

* * *

© Copyright 2007-2013 Simply Super Software. All rights reserved.

|  |    
---|---|---
